Md Faisal Hossain

Cumilla, Bangladesh



hello.faisalhossain@outlook.com





in linkedin.com/in/mdfaisalhossain1

https://web-faisal.github.io/profile/

Profile

Hi, this is Faisal. I am a Programmer. Experienced Data Entry Operator with a demonstrated history of working in the government administration industry. Skilled in Python (programming Language), JavaScript (programming Language), HTML (Hyper Text Markup Language), CSS (Cascading Style Sheets), SCSS (Senior Citizens Savings Scheme), Bootstrap (framework), React (framework), Node JS, Git, Bash, GitHub, Unity (game engine), Figma, Filmora X, logo Making, video editing & Microsoft office.

Experience



Programmer

Netizen IT Limited

Jan 2022 - Present (1 month +)

- · Compiled [Timeframe] budget reports, financial spreadsheets and organizational charts to support business operations and improve office organization.
- · Maintained databases, mailing lists, telephone networks, and other information to facilitate functioning of health education programs.

Data Entry Operator

Income Tax Department of UK Jan 2021 - Present (2 years 1 month +)

Game Developer

Unity Technologies

Dec 2020 - Present (1 year 2 months +)

- · Coding is the best way to have fun.
- You can create any type of program with coding.
- · You can create any kind of game with unity
- Develop original content through social listening and independent sources.

COMPUTER SKILL'S

Programming: Python (Programming Language) • JavaScript (Programming Language)

• HTML (Hyper Text Markup Language) • CSS (Cascading Style Sheets)

• SCSS (Senior Citizens Savings Scheme) • Git • Bash • Github

Framework & Library: React js • Node js • Bootstrap • MongoDB

Game Engine: Unity (Game Engine)

Applications: PyCharm, Visual Studio Code & Sublime Text

Other's: Figma, FilmoraX, Canva & Microsoft Office

Platforms: Windows OS

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING

Computer Science: Code.org

Crash course on Python: Google & FreeCodeCamp.org

Crash course on JavaScript: Data Camp

Font-End web developer: Programming Hero

INTERESTS

Programming

- Machine learning technology
- Robotics

Computer Science

Signature by Faisal